<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Stockholm City Guide</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search by name</string>
    <string name="title_activity_results">Category Results</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail">Details Activity</string>

    <string name="saturnus">"People go to Saturnus to drink large bowls of hot latte with the legendary cinnamon rolls – they are the biggest, and they’ve been described in the press as the best in town.
        A café and lunch spot with inspiration from France, where the decor has warm colors, a stone's throw from Stureplan and close to cultural attractions such as the Zita movie theater and the National Library of Sweden.</string>
    <string name="sallyochsystrar">"Calling themselves a food-spa, Voltaire serves modern vegetarian food complemented by fish and seafood. The restaurant is located in the Åhléns City department store and is a bright and relaxed oasis for busy shoppers. There is also a store selling everything from organic tea to soap and clever tools for the kitchen. "</string>
    <string name="flyingelk">"Two-star Restaurant Frantzén's little sister, The Flying Elk, is a gastropub in Gamla Stan (Old Town) inspired by a blend of Swedish culinary tradition and British pub culture. This is the place to experience the artisanal cuisine of the starred restaurant but in a simpler, somewhat more relaxed version with more reasonable prices.
        Explore the extensive beer list or visit the Gaston wine bar next door."</string>
    <string name="snickarbacken"> "A true hiden gem! Take your coffee while shopping or enjoy your breakfast together while touring a gallery.Snickarbacken 7 is a café, art gallery and concept store all in one space. The store offers a special selection of beloved items, vintage fashion, music, books, magazines and so much more. "</string>
    <string name="urbandeli"> "A popular restaurant, bar, deli and store in the heart of style-conscious SoFo. They serve most of the day’s meals here. The menu is varied and the dishes are well prepared. The trendy concept reminds you of New York."</string>
    <string name="blaporten"> "A classic destination for Stockholmers on a weekend walk or a visit to the museums of Djurgården island. Beautiful old interior, and relaxed bohemian garden. Tempting pastries and lunch dishes with a Mediterranean touch."</string>
    <string name="flippinburgers"> "Before opening Flippin' Burgers, the owner traveled around the US in search for inspiration on how to make the perfect burger. After returning home, he crowdfunded the restaurant and got started on his burger-quest.
        Now, many connoisseurs agree that he excelled. So much so that people actually lined up outside the restaurant to try it.
        To better accommodate the ever rising demand, Flippin' Burgers have now moved to a larger location but keep serving mouthwatering burgers and Ben and Jerry's milkshakes."</string>
    <string name="meatball"> "Meatballs for the People is a restaurant, bar and shop in one. As the name suggests, the classic Swedish meatball is in focus. The shop offers at least 14 kinds of meatballs made of ingredients like elk, beef and salmon. Sit down at a rustic wooden table or take your meatballs to go."</string>
    <string name="sturehof">"Sturehof is far from an ‘ordinary’ restaurant. With a proud history spanning over a century and a prime location on the south side of Stureplan in Stockholm, Sturehof is a bustling meeting place – a stage that is intensively alive from mid-morning to late at night, seven days a week, 365 days a year.
    Steeped in tradition, Sturehof is at the same time a modern restaurant classic on par with famous brasseries in New York and Paris. Sturehof is also a stage for art exhibitions, concerts and artist performances. The audience is a glorious mix of ages, origins, professions, and interests – in every conceivable way."</string>
    <string name="old_town">"Gamla Stan, the Old Town, is one of the largest and best preserved medieval city centers in Europe, and one of the foremost attractions in Stockholm. This is where Stockholm was founded in 1252.
        All of Gamla Stan and the adjacent island of Riddarholmen are like a living pedestrian-friendly museum full of sights, attractions, restaurants, cafés, bars and places to shop.
        Gamla Stan is also popular with aficionados of handicrafts, curios and souvenirs. The narrow winding cobblestone streets, with their buildings in so many different shades of gold, give Gamla Stan its unique character.."</string>
    <string name="nordic_museum">"The Nordic Museum is Sweden's largest museum of cultural history. The museum has exhibitions about life and work, trends and traditions, in Sweden from the 16th century to today. Their collections include clothes and fashion, textiles, furniture and interiors, jewelry, photography, folk art, glass and china. The Museum was founded in 1873 by Artur Hazelius."</string>
    <string name="djurgarden">"Many of the most popular museums and attractions in Stockholm can be found at Djurgarden. But the island is also the greenest of them all, part of the National City Park, with vast areas of forest and open spaces. No matter the season, a walk on Djurgården is beautiful. In some areas you will have difficulty imagining you’re in the middle of a big city.
    There are a some cafes and restaurants for pit stops along the way. A visitor’s center is located just past the bridge, providing tourist information and canoe and bike rental."</string>
    <string name="sthlm_concet_hall">"The blue Stockholm Concert Hall is situated on Hotorget in the heart of Stockholm. One of Sweden's architectonic masterpieces in the neoclassical style, the Concert Hall was built especially to house the Royal Stockholm Philharmonic Orchestra. Apart from being a venue for world-class concerts, it hosts the annual Nobel Prize Award Ceremony and the Polar Music Prizes.
        The famous Orpheus Group by the main steps was created by sculptor Carl Milles.
        Unveiled 1936, it is one of Stockholm´s best-known landmarks and a popular meeting spot. During summertime the Stockholm Concert Hall is open daily 11am-5pm, and offers guided tours, exhibitions and mini-concerts. "</string>
    <string name="rosendal">"This royal residence on the island of Djurgarden, built for King Karl XIV Johan, is an outstanding example of Swedish Empire style.
        Furniture, textiles and fixtures create an impressive overall effect, designed and manufactured by Swedish artists and artisans."</string>
    <string name="nk"> "Steeped in tradition, NK is Stockholm’s most luxurious department store, established 1915. Swedish and international fashion, cosmetics, jewelry, crystal, ceramics, design, fine foods and much more."</string>
    <string name="mood"> "New and stylish galleria with a focus on fashion and design. MOOD features niche boutiques like Rodebjer and Posh Living along with famous international brands recently established in Sweden, including Ralph Lauren and Club Monaco. When you are ready for a shopping break, you can enjoy a delicious meal in one of the popular restaurants (Boqueria, Vigårda, E.A.T.) or take in the modern art that adorns the galleria.
        MOOD Stockholm is located on Regeringsgatan, in the block that connects the Hamngatan and Bibliotekstan shopping districts."</string>
    <string name="ahlens"> "Sweden’s largest department store, with competitive prices for clothing, design, media, beauty and much more.
        Large, diverse grocery store in the basement."</string>
    <string name="diplomat">"In an impressive 1911-era Art Nouveau building on upscale Strandvagen boulevard, Hotel Diplomat offers great views of Nybroviken Bay, free spa access and a restaurant with a summer terrace. Wi-Fi is free.
        Diplomat’s modern interior was designed by renowned architect Per Öberg and combines classic elegance with contemporary design. Each room features blackout curtains, a spacious work area and quality Dux beds with premium linen. All include luxury toiletries and a flat-screen TV with free on-demand movies.
        The in-house T/Bar restaurant uses fresh, local produce to create classic Swedish dishes with a Mediterranean twist. The waterfront terrace is an ideal spot to take in the waterfront views during summer. Guests can enjoy a glass of champagne or cocktail at the bar after a day exploring Stockholm.
        For relaxation or fitness needs, the hotel has a spacious, well-equipped gym, a sauna and a hot tub.
        The Diplomat is just 950 feet from Stockholm’s Royal Theatre. Local buses stops right outside the hotel. Archipelago-bound boats depart regularly across the street. "</string>
    <string name="grand">"Grand Hôtel Stockholm is on the waterfront across from the Royal Palace and the Old Town, 0.6 miles from Central Train Station. It features fine dining, a luxury spa and free WiFi access.
        Grand’s soundproof, air-conditioned rooms have an LCD TV with satellite channels. Rooms also offer courtyard, city or waterfront views.
        Restaurant Mathias Dahlgren was awarded 2 Michelin stars and Mathias Dahlgren Matbaren with 1 star. The Verandan restaurant offers waterfront, city views and breakfast buffet, and Cadier Baren serves à la carte breakfast, lunch and cocktails.
        Grand Hôtel Nordic Spa and Fitness has exercise equipment and an indoor pool. Spa treatments include facials, foot massages and naprapathy.
        Grand Stockholm also offers chauffeur-driven limousine transportation and 24-hour room service."</string>
    <string name="berns">"This stylish boutique hotel is next to Nybrokajen Harbour in central Stockholm. It features a historic dining hall, lobby art exhibitions and rooms with iPod docking stations and free wired internet. Stureplan Square is a 3-minute walk away.
        In an impressive 1863 building, the Berns Hotel has elegant rooms with modern décor, luxury beds and designer linen. Fresh fruit and fashion magazines are also available.
        Berns Hotel’s intimate French bistro overlooks Berzelii Park. Asian specialties and a popular breakfast buffet can be enjoyed under a gold-coated ceiling and antique chandeliers. A popular concert venue and nightclub are also housed in Hotel Berns. Sightseeing boats and archipelago tours depart from the nearby harbor."</string>
    <string name="search_title">search_title</string>
    <string name="favorites">favorites</string>

    <string name="nordic_museum_name">"Nordic Museum"</string>
    <string name="djurgarden_name">"Djurgarden"</string>
    <string name="rosendal_name"> "Rosendal"</string>
    <string name="sthlm_concet_hall_name">"Stockholm Concert Hall"</string>
    <string name="old_town_name">"Old Town"</string>

    <string name="sallyochsystrar_name">"Sally och Systrar"</string>
    <string name="flyingelk_name">"The Flying Elk"</string>
    <string name="snickarbacken_name">"Snickarbacken"</string>
    <string name="urbandeli_name">"Urban Deli"</string>
    <string name="blaporten_name">"Bla Porten"</string>
    <string name="meatball_name">"Meatballs for the people"</string>
    <string name="flippinburgers_name">"Flipping Burger"</string>
    <string name="sturehof_name">"Sturehof"</string>
    <string name="saturnus_name">"Saturnus"</string>

    <string name="mood_name">"Mood"</string>
    <string name="ahlens_name">"Ahlens"</string>
    <string name="nk_name">"Nordiska Kompaniet"</string>

    <string name="grand_name">"Grand Hôtel"</string>
    <string name="diplomat_name">"Hotel Diplomat"</string>
    <string name="berns_name">"Berns"</string>
    
    <string name="neighborhood_norrmalmvasa">"Norrmalm/Vasastan"</string>
    <string name="neighborhood_ostermalm">"Ostermalm"</string>
    <string name="neighborhood_sodermalm">"Sodermalm"</string>
    <string name="neighborhood_djurgarden">"Djurgarden"</string>

    <string name="sallyochsystrar_web">http://www.sallyochsystrar.com"</string>
    <string name="flyingelk_web">http://www.theflyingelk.com"</string>
    <string name="google_web">http://www.google.com"</string>
</resources>
